Angrier. Deadlier. Sexier.
American Psycho II: All American Girl is a horror,
thriller film directed by Morgan J. Freeman.
Rachel is a criminology student hoping to land a position as a
teacher's assistant for professor Robert Starkman.
She's sure this position will pave the way to an FBI career, and she's willing
to do anything to obtain it -- including killing her classmates.
The school psychiatrist, Dr.
Daniels, becomes aware that Rachel is insane, but Rachel is skilled
at her dangerous game of death and identity theft.
Rachael, played by Mila Kunis.
Daniels, played by Geraint Wyn Davies.
Starkman, played by William Shatner.
Brian, played by Robin Dunne.
Cassandra, played by Lindy Booth.
Harvey, played by Neil Crone.
American Psycho 2 (also known as American Psycho II: All American Girl) is a
2002 American black comedy slasher film directed by Morgan J.
Freeman from a screenplay by Alex Sanger and Karen Craig.
Starring Mila Kunis and William Shatner, it is a stand-alone
sequel to the film American Psycho (2000).
Kunis portrays a criminology student who seeks to advance
her career by murdering her classmates.
The screenplay for the film, entitled The Girl Who Wouldn't Die,
originally had no association with American Psycho.
After production began, the script was altered to
connect the film with the original.
American Psycho 2 was released direct-to-video on June 18, 2002.
The film was panned by critics; the script was also denounced by Bret Easton Ellis, the author
of the original novel, and Kunis later expressed regret for working on the film.
The film explores themes of competition,
psychopath, fbi, dark comedy, serial killer.
The tone is dark and intense.